<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Jake Janousek&#39;s GitHub Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Jake Janousek&#39;s GitHub Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How did the Blue Bloods fare from the 2020 season to 2021?</title>
      <link>/post/2021/04/04/how-did-the-blue-bloods-fare-from-the-2020-season-to-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/04/04/how-did-the-blue-bloods-fare-from-the-2020-season-to-2021/</guid>
      <description>The 2021 College Basketball season has been hard for many especially with the COVID-19 pandemic.We have seen many teams struggle even for the Blue Bloods of league. This season we saw some of the best teams digress and not compete at the level that fans have seen them in the past. Duke and Kentucky are the top headlines as how they have struggled and each finished their seasons below .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Jake Janousek</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Sophomore at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln. I am a double major in Sports Media and Commutation and Broadcasting with a minor in Political Science. My favorite thing in the world is obviously Sports. One day I hope to be in the broadcasting game as a play by play or radio host for any sports show. Other things I like to do is be around my family and friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Note on A blogdown Tutorial</title>
      <link>/note/2017/06/14/another-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/note/2017/06/14/another-note/</guid>
      <description>I just discovered an awesome tutorial on blogdown written by Alison. I have to admit this is the best blogdown tutorial I have seen so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Quick Note on Two Beautiful Websites</title>
      <link>/note/2017/06/13/a-quick-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/note/2017/06/13/a-quick-note/</guid>
      <description>To me, the two most impressive websites based on blogdown are:
 Rob J Hyndman&amp;rsquo;s personal website. Live Free or Dichotomize by Lucy and Nick et al.  I&amp;rsquo;m sure there will be more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
